Marcus **Mo**

Contact Profile

177B Haydons Road Wimbledon London SW19 8TB Becoming a post-graduate allowed for further specialism in exciting areas such as high performance computing, data mining, and advanced numerical analysis; building upon the theoretical knowledge gained from studying Mathematics. Outside of academia, my passions involve experimenting with modern web technologies to develop performant and engaging experiences.

me@marcusmo.co.uk www.marcusmo.co.uk

Programming

Education

2012-2013

Frogramming	2012 2013	risc scientific computing	THE UTILVEISITY OF WALWICK
		Parallelisation of Simultaneous Eigenvector Computations	
C, C++		Explored parallelisation techniques with respect to finding new-	
		forms via simultaneous Hecke e	igenspaces; relating to the construc-
OpenMP, MPI		tion and tabulation of elliptic curves.	
& Nvidia CUDA		A multi-threaded strategy was built, with Boost libraries, on top of	
		an existing open-source C++ serial implementation: Eclib.	
HTML5, CSS3	2009-2012	BSc Mathematics	The University of Warwick
JavaScript, jQuery		First Class (Hons.)	
	2007-2009	A-Level	Alcester Grammar School, Sixth Form
		A-Level: AAA; AS-Level: A	
	2002-2007	GCSE	St. Benedict's Catholic High School
		AS-Level: A; GCSE: A*A*A*A	*A*A*A*A; GNVQ: Distinction

MSc Scientific Computing

Experience

2009-Present LaTeX Tutorials

latextutorials couk

The University of Warwick

Designer, Developer, Chief Editor

Developed an interactive tutorial website, by compiling a database of common mathematical statements, for others to learn the type-setting language. Later collaborated with peers to provide online documentation on LaTeX, with a focus on simplicity and low-entry level experience.

The site was used as an interactive teaching aid during seminars provided by the Warwick Maths Society.

2011—Present Virtual Futures

virtualfutures.co.uk

Designer, Developer

Collaborated with organisers and artists to develop an online archive for past and future conferences; built with Wordpress.

2010-2012 **TEDxWarwick**

tedxwarwick.com

Media Team Member, Design Consultant

Designed yearly event motifs, programmes and other marketing materials. Developed the TEDxWarwick 2011 website, and Facebook marketing pages for TEDxWarwick 2012.

2011-2012 Warwick Student Cinema

Chief Editor

Organised and coordinated volunteers for copy-writing and graphics sourcing; contributing to the termly film programme. Provided training and support for QuarkXPress.

Interests

professional: software development, high performance computing, parallel programming, web development and performance, UX design **personal:** badminton, mathematics, Go, typography.